{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-2",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 2",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "grade5",
    "unit2",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 2: Our homes",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "building",
      "answer": "tòa nhà",
      "speak": "building"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "flat",
      "answer": "căn hộ",
      "speak": "flat"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "tower",
      "answer": "tháp",
      "speak": "tower"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "address",
      "answer": "địa chỉ",
      "speak": "address"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "street",
      "answer": "đường phố",
      "speak": "street"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "kilometre",
      "answer": "ki-lô-mét",
      "speak": "kilometre"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "district",
      "answer": "quận, huyện",
      "speak": "district"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "far",
      "answer": "xa",
      "speak": "far"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "near",
      "answer": "gần",
      "speak": "near"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "live",
      "answer": "sống, cư trú",
      "speak": "live"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "house",
      "answer": "ngôi nhà",
      "speak": "house"
    }
  ]
}